Once upon a time, there was a Man named Xerxes. He lived in Persia over 1,000 years ago.
He minding his own business one day when he met a straneg old man. The old man said "I'll give 
you whatever you desire, in exchange for your labor". Curious, Xerxes accepted the man's offer. 
The old man said "Retrive the large Avgil from the tree on top of mount Damavand by 48 hours".
Xerxes immediately set out for mount Damavand. To prepare, he packed water, some snacks, and brought
a dagger in case things didn't go as planned.



So this is it. The end of the story of our hero.
The eagles flew our MC all the way to Paris - aka Sand People' Land
The city is in ruin. Up on that Eff Tower, Shrek has his blade ready to stab the hell out of our MC.
Others would have fallen, but not our MC. Going thru the heartbreaking of 1st love, the midlife crisis, Shrek is nothing but lil bitch.
As the evil Shrek flying down on the back of Dronky, our hero jumped up with his chainsaw thinking: "Our fight will be legendary!"
It's hard to tell who will prevail. On one hand, MC has the advantage of diversity, on the other hand is Shrek.
CLASH!!!

Truc as he kneeled before Shrek said, "Do me your worst, daddy, I'll take anything from you"